A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Business Manager, Subject Files, Series 3 FA137
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject files, 1902-1965; 3
  - Pensions Scientific [Staff], 5 folders, 5" letter. GL 10/86
    - Files maintained by Henry James/Jerome D. Greene, 3 folders
      - Henry James/Jerome D. Greene files, circa 1910 1912 March 4-1913 April 1 undated; 16 p. typescript (carbon copy) (Box 47, Folder 3)
        Includes: Exchange between the Business Mgr/Board of Scientific Directors, RIMR, John D. Rockefeller, Starr J. Murphy re establishment of a pension system. Includes "A Pension System for the Institute".
      - Memorandums and notes on pensions, undated (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Drafts of various dates re pension scheme at RIMR and other institutions (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - F.T. Gates/Henry James, 1913 Feb 8, re pensions, 1913 February 8 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Exchange between Henry James/Clyde Furst, Carnegie Foundation, re pensions of other institutions (Box 47, Folder 3)
        Includes 1913 Apr 1, Clyde Furst/Henry James w/Enclosure: 1913 Mar 19, M. Curie/ Clyde Furst. (Photocopies of French and typescript translation of letter is in file). [Originals removed to file of Confidential/ Sensitive material by CK, 3 Oct 1986.] re pension system for teaching staff at M. Curie's laboratory.
      - Henry James/Jerome D. Greene Files (2), 1913 March 27-May 28 (Box 47, Folder 4)
        [File to S.F. (Simon Flexner) - See S.F. note attached.].
        Primarily exchange between Henry James and Jerome D. Greene, re pensions. Includes Minutes of RIMR Board of Trustees meeting, April 29, 1913. Also includes working notes and 1 item correspondence between Manager, RIMR/Starr J. Murphy.
      - Henry James/Jerome D. Greene Files (3), 1913 May 22-1914 January 21 (Box 47, Folder 5)
        - Minutes of a meeting of Board of Trustees, RIMR, re establishment of pension plan for members and and 500,000 gift for pensions by John D. Rockefeller, 1913 May 22
        - Newspaper clippings: New York Times, New York American and [?] re 500,000 gift for pensions for members and associate members, 1913 June 3
        - "Suggestions for Pensions at the Rockefeller Institute", 1913 May 2; 3 p. typescript (carbon copy)
        - List of members, associate members and associates citing biographical and professional information for each, 14 p. typescript (carbon copy)
  - Plans suggested by various companies, 6 folders
    [From original envelope label].
    Primarily printed material.
    - Aetna Life Insurance Co., 1937 March-April (Box 47, Folder 6)
      Includes correspondence w/Waldo R. Flinn.
    - Equitable Life Assurance Society of the United States, 1935 January-1937 March (Box 47, Folder 7)
      Includes correspondence with Waldo R. Flinn.
    - Metropolitan Life Insurance Co., 1935 February-November 1937 February-March (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - N.A.M. (National Association of Manufacturers) Labor Relations Bulletin 1936. "Federal Social Security Manual" (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association of America (T.I.A.A.), 1936, undated (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Travelers Insurance Plan (of The Presbyterian Hospital of City of New York), undated (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Schedules used in preparation of the plan for retiring allowances and group life insurance for employees (1), 1934 October 1937 December undated; 5" letter GL 10/86 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Schedules used in preparation of the plan for retiring allowances and group life insurance for employees (2) (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Pension systems of other institutions (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Los Angeles, California. Joint meeting of the Trustees of Colleges and Universities of the Pacific Northwest, 1937 February 13
      - Henry James presentation, "Concerning College Pension Plans and the Social Security Law", 14 p. duplicated copy
    - Newspaper clippings, 1935 January-April 1935 June 1935 November 1936 September-November 1937 January-March 1937 May 1937 November 1938 April 1938 May undated (Box 48, Folder 4)
      Primarily re Social Security and Unemployment Insurance plans and some re institutions/companies pension plans.
    - Various papers, statistics, etc. used in preparation of the Plan for Retiring Allowances and Group Insurance of Employees of the RI made effective in the printed booklet, 1938 December 23; 3 folders
      - Copies on which penciled notations appear (Box 48, Folder 5)
        [Kept in order found].
      - Copies on which penciled notations appear (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - One copy of various papers used in the preparation of the Plan, 1936-1938 December 23, 1939 January 5 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Various Drafts of the Plan for Retiring Allowances and Group Insurance for Employees of the RI Adopted Dec 23, 1938, 3 folders, 5" letter. GL 10/86
      - untitled, 1 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - untitled, 2 (Box 49, Folder 2)
        Kept in order found.
      - untitled, 3 (Box 49, Folder 3)
        Includes 1938 Dec 23, Herbert S. Gasser/Employees RIMR, announcement of plan for retirement allowances and group life insurance adopted by Board of Trustees, Oct 28, 1938 to be put into operation Feb 1, 1939. w/attachment re Group Life Insurance.
    - [History cards of] Members and Associate Members who have served since Jan 1, 1914 and who qualify under the present rules for retiring allowances, 1914 January 1 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      [From original envelope label] Members and Associate Members, past and present staff, who have served since Jan 1, 1914. These are eligible under the present pension rules RIMR.
    - Non-Active History Cards of Staff and Other Individuals Formerly in the Employ of the RI, 1922-1923; 7 folders
      Material used by the Actuary, Mr. Buck, in the Estimates for the Joint Committee on the Study of Retiring Allowances made during 1922-1923. [From original envelope label].
      - Hand numbered 38, 5001-5199 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Hand numbered 5200-5399, 5" letter. GL 10/86 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Hand numbered 5400-5599 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Hand numbered 5600-5799 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Hand numbered 5800-5999 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Hand numbered 6000-6199 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Hand numbered 6200-6364 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Business Manager files re scientific staff appointment letters, 1918-1958; In 5 5.5" letter size boxes
    Related Materials
    See also 349-1 (5-6).
    Includes material re promotions and salaries. Also includes material re special arrangements for scientific staff on active duty in Armed forces during WWII or those involved in government work at RU during WWII. During Simon Flexner's tenure as Director of the RI, handwritten notes by S.F. (Simon Flexner) included in files.
    Arrangement within each year by Member, Associate Member, Associate, Assistant, Fellows, Volunteers etc.
    - 1918-1919, 12/1/86 GL (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - 1919-1920 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - 1920-1921 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - 1921-1922 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - 1922-1923 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - 1928-1929, 12/1/86 GL (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - 1935-1936, 12/2/86 GL (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - 1942-1943, 12/8/86 GL (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - 1948-1949, 12/8/86 GL (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - 1953-1954, 5/18/87 BG (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Business Manager files re scientific staff appointment lists, 1924 1933-1934 1940-1955; In one 5" letter size box.
    One set of lists contain information on promotions and salaries (1940-1955) and the other a summarization of each staff person's tenure at the Rockefeller Institute (1933-1934, 1940-1955). Arrangement within each year by Member, Associate Member, Associate, Assistant, Fellows, Volunteers, etc. Also included is one folder of statistics relating to the location and occupation of former RI staff (January 1924).
    - 1933-1939 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - 1940-1943 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - 1944-1947 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - 1948-1951 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - 1952-1956 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - 1924 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Business Manager subject files re scientific staff applications denied or withdrawn from consideration, 1902-1910 1916-1948; In 11 5.5" letter boxes
    Beginning in 1916, it includes an alphabetical listing of the applicants, located in the front of each year, as well as correspondence with the applicant, their application forms, and occasionally reference letters.
    The applications for 1902-1910 are arranged strictly in chronological order and the 1916-1948 applications are arranged within each year by the applicants' last name. [Because some of the material was discovered later than the rest, the years are not in perfect sequence.]
    - A-I, 1921 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - K-V, 1921 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - W-Z, 1921 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - A-K, 1922 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - L-Z, 1922 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - 1923 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - A-F, 1928 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - G-Y, 1928 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - B-L, 1929 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - M-W, 1929 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - A-H, 1935 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - J-Z, 1935 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - A-H, 1936 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - K-S, 1936 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - S-Z, 1936 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - A-L, 1937 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - M-Z, 1937 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - 1901-1902 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - 1903 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - 1904 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - 1905 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - 1906 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - 1907 February-March (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - 1907 April-September (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - 1908 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - 1909 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - 1910 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - A-O, 1916 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - P-Z, 1916 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - A-M, 1917 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - N-Z, 1917 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - 1918 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - A-L, 1919 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - M-Z, 1919 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - A-K, 1920 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - L-Z, 1920 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - A-J, 1924 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - K-N, 1924 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - O-Z, 1924 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - A-F, 1925 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - G-O, 1925 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - P-Z, 1925 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - A-H, 1926 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - I-N, 1926 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - O-Z, 1926 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - A-J, 1927 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - K-Z, 1927 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - A-F, 1930 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - G-M, 1930 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - N-Z, 1930 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - A-G, 1931 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - H-P, 1931 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - R-Z, 1931 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - A-E, 1932 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - F-J, 1932 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - K-P, 1932 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - R-Z, 1932 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - A-G, 1933 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - H-M, 1933 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - M-Z, 1933 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - A-G, 1934 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - H-P, 1934 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - R-Z, 1934 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - A-G, 1938 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - H-M, 1938 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - N-T, 1938 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - W-Z, 1938 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - A-F, 1939 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - G-K, 1939 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - L-R, 1939 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - S-Z, 1939 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - A-K, 1940 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - L-Z, 1940 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - A-I, 1940 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - J-Z, 1941 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - 1942 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - 1943 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - 1944 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - 1945 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - 1946 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - A-K, 1947-1950 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - L-Z, 1947-1950 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Business Manager files re staff health coverage through the Associated Hospital Service of New York, 1936 February-1943; In 1.5" letter size box
    Includes correspondence concerning payments to the Associated Hospital Service's plan, coverage of children and spouses of the staff, applications, etc.
    Arranged in chronological order.
    - 1936-1937 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - 1940 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - 1941 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - 1942 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - 1943 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Business Manager Subject Files re inquiries regarding scientific staff appointments, 1932-1949; In 1.5" letter box
    Similar to "Scientific Staff Applications Denied or Withdrawn", but less formal (i.e., no filled out application forms or letters of reference).
    For 1932-1937, the letters are arranged in alphabetical order; the rest are arranged in chronological order.
    - A-F, 1932-1937 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - G-P, 1932-1937 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - R-Z, 1932-1937 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - 1938-1940 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - 1941-1944 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - 1947-1949 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Business Manager Subject Files re applications for grants denied or withdrawn, 1916-1934; In 1 1/2 5" letter boxes
    Includes application forms and correspondence, along with an alphabetical list of applicants located at the beginning of 1916, 1920, 1923, 1925, and 1930.
    For 1916-1919, the applications are arranged in chronological order; the rest are arranged in alphabetical order by the applicant's last name within each set of years.
    - A-Z, 1916-1919 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - A-L, 1920-1923 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - M-Z, 1920-1923 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - A-Z, 1923-1924 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - A-G, 1925-1929 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - H-Z, 1925-1929; 21/2" letter box (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - A-K, 1930-1934 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - L-Z, 1930-1934 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Selective Service, 1940-1947; 0.8 Cubic Feet
    Includes correspondence; also includes booklets, clippings, lists, memos, notes, and reports.
    Correspondents include Joseph Chvatal, David M. Eigner, David Kirman, George H. Michel, Kenneth Schmitt, and Harold R. Wellander concerning their experiences in World War II.
    Subjects include classifications of employees, deferments, retiring allowance contributions (correspondence with men in service concerning their contributions and their jobs at RIMR), the RIMR policy, and the Selective Service Act.
    Arranged in alphabetical order by subject.
    Conditions Governing Access
    Limited access.
    - Classifications, 1940-1943 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Deferments - Administrative Group, 1942-1944 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      Deferments are arranged in alphabetical order by person in group.
    - Deferments - Bergmann's Group, 1943-1945 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Deferments - Blum's Group, 1942 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Deferments - General, 1941-1944 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Deferments - Jacobs' Group, 1942-1944 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Deferments - New York Groups, 1943-1945 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Deferments - Northrop's Group, 1941-1945 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Deferments - Osterhout's Group, 1942-1945 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Deferments - People Who Have Left, A-E, 1941-1945 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Deferments - People Who Have Left, H-W, 1941-1945 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Deferments - Princeton Department, 1943-1945 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Deferments - Rivers' Group, 1942-1945 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Deferments - Shedlovsky's Group, 1943-1944 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Deferments - Stanley's Group, 1944 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Deferments - Stillman's Group, 1943-1945 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Deferments - Swift's Group, 1941-1945 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Retiring Allowance Contributions (RAC) - Brigante, Joseph R., 1945-1947 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - RAC - Christmann, Harold, 1943-1946 (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - RAC - Chvatal, Joseph, 1943-1945 (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - RAC - Eigner, David M., 1941-1946 (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - RAC - Faccini, Daniel F., 1943-1945 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - RAC - Feldman, Arthur, 1942-1946 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - RAC - Frampton, Elon W., 1943-1946 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - RAC - Freedman, Henry, 1943-1947 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - RAC - Gand, Rudolph, 1942-1946 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - RAC - Grace, John, 1942-1947 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - RAC - Hardison, Charles, 1942-1947 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - RAC - Kirman, David, 1940-1945 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - RAC - Krystow, Paul, 1942-1944 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - RAC - Lyon, Robert L., 1942-1947 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - RAC - Mall, Walter J., 1942 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - RAC - Markovies, George, 1943-1944 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - RAC - Michel, George H., 1941-1946 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - RAC - Millard, Harold, 1941-1942 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - RAC - Miller, Robert M., 1942-1945 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - RAC - Mullin, Robert James, 1943-1946 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - RAC - Mussler, Herbert, 1942-1947 (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - RAC - Ondayko, George, 1942-1947 (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - RAC - Quabeck, George P., 1941-1943 (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - RAC - Schmitt, Kenneth, 1943-1946 (Box 74, Folder 20)
    - RAC - Snyder, Martin, 1942-1947 (Box 74, Folder 21)
    - RAC - Turner, Eugene H., 1941-1947 (Box 74, Folder 22)
    - RAC - Turner, Frederick Arthur, 1942-1946 (Box 74, Folder 23)
    - RAC - Wellander, Harold R., 1942-1944 (Box 74, Folder 24)
    - RAC - Wilczewski, John A., 1942-1947 (Box 74, Folder 25)
    - Rockefeller Institute Policy, 1940-1945 (Box 74, Folder 26)
    - Selective Service Act - General, 1940-1945 (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - TIAA, 1936-1940; 2 folders
    Includes booklets, budgets, charts, graphs, and minutes.
    Subjects include the retiring allowance plan for non-academic employees.
    - Retiring Allowance Plan for Employees (Non-Academic) I, 1936-1940 (Box 74, Folder 28)
    - Retiring Allowance Plan for Employees (Non-Academic) II, 1936-1940 (Box 74, Folder 29)
  - War Demonstration Hospital, 1914-1922; 4 folders
    Includes correspondence; also includes blueprints, booklets, budgets, equipment lists, minutes, notes, and photographs.
    Subjects include the dispensation of the War Demonstration Hospital at the end of World War I and the Rockefeller Foundation funding of war research and relief.
    Limited access
    - 1917-1918 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - 1919-1922 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Photos & The WDH: Its Plan and Construction, 1917 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - War Demonstrations Hospital - War Research and Financing, 1914-1918 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - War Labor Board, 1941-1944; 0.2 Cubic Feet
    Includes correspondence and wage schedules.
    Subjects include salary increases for employees.
    - War Labor Board, 1941-1942 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - War Labor Board, 1943 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - War Labor Board, 1944 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - War Risk Insurance, 1918 1942-1944; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 8)
    Includes correspondence; also includes lists.
    Subjects include the War Risk Insurance Act (1917) and the RIMR's bearing the cost of the insurance for the scientific staff involved in both world wars.
  - World War II, 1940-1948; 0.4 Cubic Feet
    Includes correspondence; also includes bulletins, forms, instructions to staff, lists, and statistics.
    Subjects include air raids, building wardens, and rationing. The rationing material is mainly routine correspondence between the RIMR and the Office of Price Administration concerning allotments of food and fuel.
    - World War II - Air Raids, 1942-1943 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - World War II - Building Wardens, 1941-1942 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - World War II - General, 1940-1948 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Rationing - Bank Account, 1943 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Rationing - Basic Data, 1941-1943 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Rationing - Basic Data, 1944-1947 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Rationing - Butter, 1943-1945 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Rationing - Foods, 1943-1945 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Rationing - Foods, 1946-1947 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Rationing - Forms, 1943 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Rationing - Fuel Oil, 1942-1945 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Rationing - Interoffice Letters, 1942-1947 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Rationing - Navy Allotments-Letters to Drew, 1943-1946 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Rationing - Navy Allotments, Reports, & Communications, 1943-1944 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Rationing - Navy Allotments, Reports, & Communications, 1945-1946 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Rationing - OPA Correspondence, 1942-1944 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Rationing - OPA Correspondence, 1945-1947 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Rationing - Point Charts, 1943 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Rationing - Sugar File, 1942-1943 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Rationing - White Gasoline, 1943-1945 (Box 77, Folder 5)